oneworld.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy | oneworld

### Protecting Your Privacy

You are our top priority, in the skies and on the web. We follow these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy to protect your personal information. It details the information we collect, how we use it, when it is shared with others and how we safeguard its confidentiality and security.

### Who We Are?

 **one** world Management Company, Inc. (“oneworld”) is a Delaware corporation with offices at 2 Park Avenue, Suite 1100, New York, NY 10016.

### Our Member Airlines and Their Services

 **one** world manages as an alliance of airlines and affiliates (“Member Airlines”). For more information, visit [_www.oneworld.com_](https://www.oneworld.com/oneworld-connect).

Business with any Member Airline or any others, including any arranged via this website, will be governed exclusively under their respective contracts of carriage (which may be published under varying titles) or other terms specified by such other third party regardless of any conflict with these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. None shall be jointly or severally liable with any other or with **one** world and none will be deemed to have consented to the application of any law or jurisdiction of any court because their services were arranged or otherwise obtained or contracted for via this website. **one** world shall not be liable, regardless of the theory on such a claim may be based, for the performance or failure to perform, by any Member Airline or any others.

### Collecting Personal Information

We collect personal information to: (i) provide the various services offered via this website, including orders/reservations for services to be provided by Member Airlines and others, (ii) better understand your needs, and (iii) aggregate information with our Member Airlines and others for analysis. This information is collected from a variety of sources, including: (i) when you provide us with information, (ii) when your internet browser connects to our website, (iii) **one** world Member Airlines, and (iv) third parties who provide other services to you. By providing your personal information via this website you consent to its collection. The personal information we collect through these various sources may include, but is not limited to: (i) name, birth date, addresses and information from state issued identifications, including passports, (ii) email addresses, telephone, fax and pager numbers, (iii) credit card and frequent flyer account information, (iv) travel information, including flight selections, travel dates, other information associated with such travel and obtained via this website, including for accommodations, vehicle rentals, food and other selections, (v) nationality and country of residence, (vi) use of self-service devices, flight status notifications and online check-in, (vii) information provided via survey, focus group or other market research activity, and (viii) information provided to travel agents and/or customer service representatives.

Personal information collected will be retained until services obtained via this website are completed, which for those with a continuing relationship, e.g., an account or membership, will be until that account is closed or membership is ended, plus the period of time for which they must be retained to comply with applicable law and/or are subject to audit.

Residents of the European Union have certain rights under EU law to request access to “Personal Data” we collect and/or process, as well as to request modification, deletion or limitations on use or transfer of such information. If you are an EU resident and would like to make such a request, please contact [_privacyofficer@oneworld.com_](mailto:privacyofficer@oneworld.com). Proof of identity and/or authority may be required.

### Cookies

A “cookie” is file that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. Such cookies are needed to facilitate the provision of certain functions of this website. By using this website, you consent to the receipt of such cookies.

### Do Not Track Signals

This website does not respond to do not track signals.

### Aggregate Information

When you visit this website, we may use cookies, tags and associated technologies to collect non-personal information such as your browser type, your operating system, the name of your internet service provider and the web pages you have visited. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Information that does not identify you personally, including from which personally identifiable information has been removed, is not subject to the limitations on disclosure in these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

### Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please note that these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy apply only to information collected by **one** world via this website. **one** world is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites or by third parties.

### Who Do We Share Your Personal Information With?

To respond to inquiries that you may send via this website, for example, with regard to availability of services, we may share your information with third-party processors that provide such information. To provide you with services that are provided by third parties, including our Member Airlines, we may share your personal information with such third parties and/or thirty-party processors that receive such data on their behalf, for example, that accept and make applicable airline reservations and/or process payments. Such parties are based in the various countries in which our Member Airlines, such third-party service providers and/or their third-party processors are based, including, without limitation, Argentina, Australia, Brazil, Chile, China, Colombia, Ecuador, Finland, Germany, Japan, Jordan, Malaysia, Morocco, Peru, Qatar, Russia, Spain, Sri Lanka, the United Kingdom, and the United States. Such parties may share your personal information in furtherance of the provision of those services. Each such party receiving such personal information may also use such personal information as specified in their own privacy policies (if any). In those cases, in which you identify yourself as part of a group or as an employee of an employer in connection with ordering services via this site, for example, by those making reservations or obtaining training via this website, we may share information regarding such use with such group and/or employer.

### Charges and Credit Card Information

When you order services via this website, we may collect and process credit card information from you that will be shared as provided above. To pay for certain services ordered, please follow instructions provided. Credit card information will be handled and used in accordance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS).

### Marketing Communication and Promotions

 **one** world and third parties acting on our behalf may contact you via e-mail with marketing communication and promotional offers unless you have opted out of receiving such communications, which may be done via links appearing in each such electronic communication.

### Disclaimer

 **one** world makes no representation and gives no warranty (either express or implied) as to this website’s completeness or accuracy of the information that it contains or that is provided via this website. All implied terms including, but not limited to merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or non-infringement are hereby disclaimed. **one** world does not warrant that this site will operate without interruptions, be timely, secure or error-free. **one** world does not warrant that the site or its contents are free from viruses or problems and **one** world is not responsible for any harm caused by use of this website. **one** world’s absolute limit of liability in all cases and for any claim whatsoever based on or related to this site, will be, in the aggregate, one US dollar. **one** world will not be liable for any special, indirect or consequential loss you may suffer, even if informed of the possibility of such damages. **one** world will not be liable for any loss of profits, loss of business, loss of data, loss of contracts, loss of savings, loss of use or any other economic loss.

### Trademark and Copyright

Trademarks, brands and copyright material contained on this website belong to **one** world Alliance, LLC or the applicable Member Airline or third party. No such materials may be reproduced without the prior written consent of the applicable owners, except for personal use in a non-public fashion. No information provided via this website may be republished in any fashion in any public forum. Automated access to this website, for example, via a “screen scraper,” “bot,” etc. is prohibited.

### Severability

If, for any reason, any portion of these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy will be determined by a competent authority, i.e., court or arbitrator, to be void or unenforceable, then (a) that portion will be of no effect, (b) the balance will remain in full force and effect, and (c) these Terms and Conditions will be interpreted and performed as though the stricken portion were replaced with a valid and enforceable provision that comes as close as possible to expressing the intention of the stricken provision.

### Choice of Law and Venue

Regardless of their own location, all data provided by users of this website and all business conducted via this website are done in the United States. These Terms of Use and Privacy Policy will be governed and construed under the laws of the United States and the State of New York without regard to otherwise applicable conflict of laws statutes and rules and subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the federal courts of Southern District of New York without regard to claims of that being an inconvenient forum. You waive all right to trial by jury in any action, proceeding or counterclaim arising out of or in connection with these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. Any judgment obtained from the foregoing court will be enforceable in any court of competent jurisdiction. You agree to reimburse **one** world for any costs incurred by **one** world in defending any matter brought in a court other than that allowed hereunder or for any claim in excess of that permitted hereunder. Any court will be permitted and is directed to grant the foregoing relief.

### Contact

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about the way in which your personal information is collected or used by **one** world or desire, for a legitimate purpose, to access, review or correct such information, please contact the **one** world Privacy Officer at [_privacyofficer@oneworld.com_](mailto:privacyofficer@oneworld.com). To ensure that privacy is maintained, communications regarding personal information previously provided may only be done via the e-mail address provided when such information was originally provided, and proof of identity may be required.

### Changes

 **one** world reserves the right to modify these Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, including retroactively, at any time without prior notice.

Updated: June 2019
